So here's my complete solution for the if statement in our train.py file.
下面说说我是如何编写 train.py 文件中的 if 语句的
The first thing I wanted to do was add
首先向 parser 中添加
arguments to our parser for our three model parameters.
三个模型参数
I've specified input_dim, hidden_dim, and output _dim.
我指定了 input_dim hidden_dim 和 output _dim
All of these arguments are going to be integer values,
这三个参数都是整数值
and I've specified default values for each.
并且我都指定了默认值
Input_dim is the number of input features to our model
Input_dim 表示输入特征的数量
which will default to two since we have two-dimensional data.
默认为 2 因为数据是二维的
Hidden_dim is the hidden dimension of the model which I'll set as a default to 10.
Hidden_dim 表示隐藏维度 默认为 10
Finally, output_dim is the output dimension of
最后 output_dim 表示输出维度
our model or how many values I want to output,
或我想输出多少个值
and I'll just want to output one class score.
我只想输出一个类别分数
The next to do was to instantiate the model by passing in the appropriate parameters.
下个任务是传入相应的参数并实例化模型
I know how to instantiate a SimpleNet.
我知道如何实例化 SimpleNet
I just have to pass in the appropriate input dimension,
只需传入合适的输入维度
hidden dimension, and output dimension.
隐藏维度和输出维度
Setting these equal to args.input_dim will allow someone
将它们设为等于 args.input_dim
to specify this dimension when they instantiate an estimator.
使我们能够在实例化 estimator 时指定这些维度
I'm also moving this model to
我还将这个模型移到了合适的设备上
the appropriate device which will move it to a GPU if it's available.
如果有 GPU 就移到 GPU 上
Next, I'm choosing to use an Adam optimizer which is just my go-to because,
接下来选择使用 Adam 优化器
empirically, it works pretty well,
因为经验表明它很好用
but you could also use stochastic gradient descent.
但是你也可以使用随机梯度下降法
I'm passing in my model parameters here and
在这里传入模型参数
the learning rates specified in my parameters.
以及学习速率
Then, for my criterion,
对于 criterion
I'm specifying BCELoss, which is binary cross entropy loss.
我指定为 BCELoss 即二元交叉熵损失
In PyTorch, normal cross entropy will not work
在 PyTorch 中 这时候普通的交叉熵损失不可行
here because our model only returns one value,
因为模型仅返回一个值
and so it's particularly suited to BCELoss.
BCELoss 非常适合
That completes this if statement.
if 语句就编写完了
My complete model, optimizer,
完整的 model optimizer和 criterion
and criterion will be passed into this train function which will save our trained model.
将传递到这个 train 函数中 它将保存训练过的模型
Now, if we go back to our notebook,
现在回到 notebook
I can use pygmentize to print out our complete train.py file.
我可以使用 !pygmentize 输出完整的 train.py 文件
The next step is going to be creating and training a PyTorch estimator such
下一步是创建和训练一个 PyTorch estimator
that it executes this training script and trains on the training data we stored in S3.
它将执行此训练脚本并使用在 S3 上存储的训练数据进行训练
A PyTorch estimator is constructed in a very similar way to other estimators.
PyTorch estimator 的结构与其他 estimator 很相似
You can see that I'm importing a PyTorch estimator here,
我在这里导入了 PyTorch estimator
and you'll just have to pass in some arguments to the constructor.
你只需向构造函数传入一些参数
When a custom model is constructed in SageMaker,
在 SageMaker 中构建自定义模型时
an entry point must be specified that points to a training script, in this case.
必须指定一个入口点 在此例中入口点指向训练脚本
The entry point will let it know where the training script is
入口点会告诉 estimator 训练脚本在哪
located so that the estimator knows what to do when.fit is called.
这样的话 当 .fit 被调用时 estimator 知道该怎么办
So I've given you a link to just the documentation for a PyTorch estimator and I
我提供了 PyTorch estimator 的参考文档链接
think you'll be able to complete this task and train
我认为仅参考此文档
a custom model by just using this as a resource.
你就能完成此任务并训练自定义模型
Try that on your own,
请试着自己完成任务
and in the next video, I'll go over one solution.
我将在下个视频中介绍我的解决方案